<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fonticons Blog</title>
    <description>The Official Fonticons Blog</description>
    <link>http://blog.fonticons.com</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.fonticons.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year, New Feature, and New Updates!</title>
      <description>&lt;h3&gt;Custom Icons!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Everything’s shiny, Cap’n.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What could possibly be better than adding a sweet icon to your kit from one of our family of icon fonts?
Why, a most excellent icon you designed yourself, of course!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dave and I are really pumped to announce the
availability of custom icons in Fonticons. Upload your SVG, then you can add your custom icon to any of your kits.
We&amp;#39;re already using this feature today on the blog!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to some great user feedback, our Free plan now has the ability to try out
custom icons as well! We really think you&amp;#39;re going to love adding your own custom icons.
And if you don&amp;#39;t yet have a Fonticons account, you can &lt;a href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/request/new&quot;&gt;request an invite&lt;/a&gt; today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Font Awesome Black Tie&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Black Tie is going through some finishing touches, and Dave says it should be ready soon. We are happy to announce that
Black Tie will be available for our Freelancer, Studio, and Agency plans!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Font Awesome 4.3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Font Awesome 4.3 should be coming soon, and we&amp;#39;ll have it added to Fonticons shortly thereafter. Make sure you get in your icon
requests added to &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/FortAwesome/Font-Awesome/issues&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Thank You!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you to all those that have signed up and tried out Fonticons. We are constantly striving to make
Fonticons the best platform for icons on the web. We appreciate all feedback and hope to make 2015 a banner
year.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <link>http://blog.fonticons.com/2015/01/02/new-year-new-feature-new-updates/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.fonticons.com/2015/01/02/new-year-new-feature-new-updates/</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invites and Custom Icons</title>
      <description>&lt;h3&gt;Invitations are going out!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Travis and I are crazy excited (yep, again), because we just sent out the first batch of Fonticons Beta invitations!
We&amp;#39;re rolling them out slowly to make sure everything goes smoothly. If you already
&lt;a href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/request/new&quot;&gt;requested for an invitation&lt;/a&gt;, you should be getting it in the next few days!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any issues or usability suggestions, please please talk to us! As we said in our last post, the easiest
way to get in touch with us is our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hipchat.com/g1K5ugavM&quot;&gt;public channel on HipChat&lt;/a&gt; (during US business
hours). Otherwise, hit us up on email at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:dave@fonticons.com&quot;&gt;dave@fonticons.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:travis@fonticons.com&quot;&gt;travis@fonticons.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Up Next: Custom Icons&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, we&amp;#39;re working on implementing custom icons for the beta. I&amp;#39;ve mapped out use cases, workflows, and the
HTML &amp;amp; CSS prototypes are ready to go. Today, Travis is starting implementation. We&amp;#39;re expecting to have those ready
sometime in the next month.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <link>http://blog.fonticons.com/2014/11/05/invites-and-custom-icons/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.fonticons.com/2014/11/05/invites-and-custom-icons/</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Fonticons</title>
      <description>&lt;p class=&quot;info initial-icon&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-newspaper-o&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
After several months of hard work, &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/supercodepoet&quot;&gt;Travis&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/davegandy&quot;&gt;I&lt;/a&gt; are crazy excited to announce a limited release of the Fonticons beta.
Interested? Head on over to &lt;a href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/request/new&quot;&gt;request an invitation&lt;/a&gt; and we&#39;ll get you one
as soon as we can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Fonticons makes web icons fast and easy.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
With Fonticons, you&amp;#39;ll be able to choose just the right icon set to match the look and feel of your website and get
just the icons and CSS you need &amp;mdash; making your site load faster.
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Icon Fonts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think this is the beginning of a beautiful friendship.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Icon fonts are a great way to get scalable vector graphics on your website and have complete control over them with
CSS. That&amp;#39;s why I created &lt;a href=&quot;http://fontawesome.io&quot;&gt;Font Awesome&lt;/a&gt; a couple of years ago. Font Awesome gives you a
large set of scalable vector icons for just about anything your site needs. Font Awesome&amp;#39;s CSS features make it even
easier to use icons at larger sizes, as bullets, or even spin, stack, and rotate icons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://meanpath.com/f/HcZE2d&quot;&gt;According to meanpath&lt;/a&gt;, Font Awesome is now on almost 3 million websites. And we
continue to see more and more traffic every month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Why Fonticons?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I&amp;#39;m your huckleberry.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As simple and powerful as icon fonts are to use, they aren&amp;#39;t perfect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, people visiting your website have to download every single icon in the set. Our research shows that most websites
only use around 20 icons total. Font Awesome, for example, has almost 500 icons. That&amp;#39;s a lot of icons going across the
wire that your site isn&amp;#39;t using. And there&amp;#39;s likely a good bit of CSS you don&amp;#39;t need either. That slows your site down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, what if your icon set doesn&amp;#39;t have the exact icon you need? Or what if you want to serve up your company logo?
Creating your own icon font is no simple task. You&amp;#39;ll need to learn a typesetting tool, figure out how font metrics work,
make your icons pixel perfect, export to the right webfont formats, figure out the CSS to integrate everything, then get
your web server to serve up the custom font to every browser without cross-site failures. It&amp;#39;s a big bag of hurt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Web icons should easier. That&amp;#39;s why we made Fonticons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Speed up Your Website&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Faster! Faster! Faster would be better!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since Fonticons allows you to load just the icons and CSS your website uses, you&amp;#39;ll drastically speed up their load time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, if this blog were using stock Font Awesome 4.2.0, our icons and CSS would weigh in at 87.4kB.
Using Fonticons, this blog&amp;#39;s kit weighs in at 4.06kB. That&amp;#39;s a &lt;strong&gt;95% bandwidth savings&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Tons of Icon Sets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We need to talk about your flair.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like Helvetica isn&amp;#39;t the perfect typographic font for every website on earth, one single icon set isn&amp;#39;t
perfect for everyone either. The right set of icons reinforces the exact look and feel you need. We believe iconography
should have the same level of variety, beauty, and refinement seen in traditional typography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To give you the best icon sets to choose from, we&amp;#39;ve scoured the web and heavily curated just the right ones. We&amp;#39;ve made
sure each set has a large number of icons, so you&amp;#39;ll be more likely to find the perfect icon when you need it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Curious? &lt;a href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/fonts&quot;&gt;Check out our icon sets &amp;raquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We&amp;#39;re carefully adding new icon sets as we find just the right ones. Think we&amp;#39;re missing a set?
&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:dave@fonticons.com&quot;&gt;Let me know&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Powerful, Simple CSS Toolkit&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I&amp;#39;m giving her all she&amp;#39;s got, Captain!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;ve paired the best icon sets with Font Awesome&amp;#39;s powerful CSS toolkit. That makes it easier to control and style your
icons exactly the way you need. You can also pare down to just the CSS your site needs, making your kit load even faster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Served up from a CDN&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She&amp;#39;ll make it point-five past lightspeed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;ve partnered up with &lt;a href=&quot;http://maxcdn.com&quot;&gt;MaxCDN&lt;/a&gt; to serve your icons wicked fast. Their global network means your kit
loads faster and more reliably anywhere in the world. Even our free accounts are served by MaxCDN!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;PS. We love you, MaxCDN. You&amp;#39;ve been hosting Font Awesome on BootstrapCDN since the early days. You&amp;#39;re awesome!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Custom Icons &amp;mdash; COMING SOON!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good. Now I know what to get you for your birthday.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to add your company logo to your kit? Or anything else you can imagine? Fonticons makes it easy to upload and
manage your own custom vector icons. We&amp;#39;re adding this to Fonticons right now, so it should be ready soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Beta?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Boy, that escalated quickly&amp;hellip;”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now, Fonticons is a beta product. To us, that means you might occasionally run into an issue here or there. Let us
know ASAP, and we&amp;#39;ll get it fixed up quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Talk to Us&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Message for you, sir.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every day, we&amp;#39;re making Fonticons better. Improving reliability, adding features, simplifying the user experience. But
we can&amp;#39;t do that alone. We need your input and feedback to constantly make things better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;d love to hear from you. Our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hipchat.com/g1K5ugavM&quot;&gt;public channel on HipChat&lt;/a&gt; is the
best way to talk to us during normal US business hours. If we&amp;#39;re not around on HipChat, try emailing us at
&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:dave@fonticons.com&quot;&gt;dave@fonticons.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:travis@fonticons.com&quot;&gt;travis@fonticons.com&lt;/a&gt;. We&amp;#39;ll get back to you as soon as we can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Request an Invitation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Aaaaaas&amp;hellip; Yoooooou&amp;hellip; Wiiiiiish&amp;hellip;”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to try out Fonticons? Head on over to &lt;a href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/request/new&quot;&gt;request an invitation&lt;/a&gt; and we&amp;#39;ll get you
one soon. We&amp;#39;re adding new users just as fast as we can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;sign-up&quot; href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/request/new&quot;&gt;Request an Invitation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <link>http://blog.fonticons.com/2014/10/23/introducing-fonticons/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.fonticons.com/2014/10/23/introducing-fonticons/</guid>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
