<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fonticons Blog</title>
    <description>The Official Fonticons Blog</description>
    <link>http://blog.fonticons.com</link>
    <atom:link href="http://blog.fonticons.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Stay, Unicode, Stay. Good Unicode.</title>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You said stay so I stayed.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the best things about my job is getting to deliver a feature our awesome 
users have asked for. Today, I am happy to announce changes to how unicode
values our handled in your kits!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before when you added icons to a kit we waited until you published the kit to 
assign a unicode value to it. The problem was that when you removed an earlier
icon all the unicode values could get shuffled when publishing the kit again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now when you add an icon to a kit we generate its unicode value right then. You have
the ability to change this value on the &amp;quot;Tweak Kit&amp;quot; tab of your kit&amp;#39;s settings.
You can also see these values in the kit&amp;#39;s documentation found under the &amp;quot;Publish Kit&amp;quot;
tab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this change we hope make the transition from regular Font Awesome to using 
Fonticons much easier. We also hope that this will allow our users to do some
new and amazing things in their CSS with their kits. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We try very hard to make Fonticons the best it can be. We&amp;#39;re always listening
to new suggestions, so keep&amp;#39;em coming!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <link>http://blog.fonticons.com/2015/05/12/stay-unicode-stay/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.fonticons.com/2015/05/12/stay-unicode-stay/</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copy &amp; Paste from Illustrator CC, Enterprise Services, and Free Accounts</title>
      <description>&lt;h3&gt;Copy &amp;amp; Paste from Illustrator CC!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just minutes ago, we added the ability to copy from Illustrator CC and paste directly into a new custom icon on Fonticons!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All you have to do is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open up your vector file in Illustrator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select and copy the icon you&amp;#39;d like to add to Fonticons. The icon needs to be a single color vector with non-overlapping paths.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Switch over to Fonticons and click on &amp;quot;Your Custom Icons,&amp;quot; then &amp;quot;Add Icon.&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Name your icon, then paste into the &amp;quot;Paste from Illustrator CC&amp;quot; field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Submit your icon, and you&amp;#39;re good to go!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Travis put together a snazzy video:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;630&quot; height=&quot;354&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Zs8wibDbf3w?VQ=HD720&amp;rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Enterprise Services&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;ve had a considerable amount of interest from folks who are looking for more than the 10 million pageviews our Agency
plan provides. So we&amp;#39;re proud to announce our &lt;a href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/start#enterprise&quot;&gt;custom Enterprise services&lt;/a&gt;!
You&amp;#39;ll get all the great things from our other Fonticons plans, plus VIP support, and any number of pageviews your
business needs! Interested? Just &lt;a href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/start#enterprise&quot;&gt;fill out our form&lt;/a&gt;, and we&amp;#39;ll get back to you
right quick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The Free Plan is Back!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After much consideration, we&amp;#39;ve decided to bring back the Fonticons Free Plan! Feel free to head on over to the
&lt;a href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/start&quot;&gt;sign up page&lt;/a&gt; and select the Free Plan.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <link>http://blog.fonticons.com/2015/04/20/copy-paste-enterprise-services-free-plan/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.fonticons.com/2015/04/20/copy-paste-enterprise-services-free-plan/</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kit Download and Annual Billing</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At Fonticons, we&amp;#39;re hard at work every day making things better. We listen closely to each and every conversation
we have to see where we should make changes. You&amp;#39;ve given us a ton of great feedback and ideas, so thank you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Kit Download&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most common request we&amp;#39;ve had is for the ability to download your kits. If you&amp;#39;ve got your own asset workflow or CDN,
it can be important to have full control over where things are served from.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we&amp;#39;re proud to announce that you can now download directly from the &amp;quot;Publish Kit&amp;quot;
step when you&amp;#39;re editing your kit!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/2015-03-19-kit-download.png&quot; alt=&quot;Kit Download&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;ve also got some more improvements coming soon for kit download:
- Full kit documentation as a static HTML file
- Woff2 support!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Annual Billing&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To enable Kit Download, you&amp;#39;ll need to switch to Annual Billing. We&amp;#39;re also throwing in 2 free months when you switch!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s a link right under the Download Kit button:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/2015-03-19-annual-billing.png&quot; alt=&quot;Annual Billing&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;More to Come!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;ve got a lot more up our sleeves to make Fonticons better, so stay tuned. Have any issues, ideas, or thoughts? Drop
us a note at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:support@fonticons.com&quot;&gt;support@fonticons.com&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <link>http://blog.fonticons.com/2015/03/19/kit-download-and-annual-billing/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.fonticons.com/2015/03/19/kit-download-and-annual-billing/</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Tie!</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;re super excited to announce the addition of Black Tie to Fonticons! It is immediately available for folks on the
Freelancer, Studio, and Agency plans!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Black Tie?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Black Tie is the first commercial icon set I&amp;#39;ve created, and I&amp;#39;m really proud of it. The big idea behind Black Tie is
that icons should come in different visual weights, just as different font weights are an important part of traditional
typography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stylistically, my goal with Black Tie was to create a clean, minimalist set of icons that will feel right at home next to
modern sans-serif fonts like Helvetica and Proxima Nova. You can check out the
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/232193852/font-awesome-black-tie&quot;&gt;Kickstarter page&lt;/a&gt; to see the story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s a sneak peek (I&amp;#39;m especially proud of cut, copy and paste):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;icon-showoff&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-star-bts&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-book-bts&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-warning-bts&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-key-bts&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-flag-bts&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-phone-bts&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-cut-bts&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-copy-bts&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-paste-bts&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-star-btb&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-book-btb&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-warning-btb&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-key-btb&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-flag-btb&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-phone-btb&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-cut-btb&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-copy-btb&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-paste-btb&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-star-btm&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-book-btm&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-warning-btm&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-key-btm&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-flag-btm&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-phone-btm&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-cut-btm&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-copy-btm&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-paste-btm&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-star-btl&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-book-btl&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-warning-btl&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-key-btl&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-flag-btl&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-phone-btl&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-cut-btl&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-copy-btl&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-paste-btl&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to see the full set? Head on over to &lt;a href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/fonts&quot;&gt;Fonticons&lt;/a&gt; to check out the 4 different weights.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <link>http://blog.fonticons.com/2015/03/04/black-tie/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.fonticons.com/2015/03/04/black-tie/</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changes and Updates</title>
      <description>&lt;h3&gt;Invites, Invites, Invites&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday we sent out several thousand invites to many of you that have been waiting. The response has been overwhelming and
we&amp;#39;re adding capacity to handle the increased traffic! Thanks for being patient as we iron things out a bit. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Changes to Plans&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/2015-01-29-plans.png&quot; alt=&quot;Changes to Plans&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, we added the Blogger plan at $4 a month. This plan is designed to meet the needs of some of our more casual users
that also want access to lots of great icon sets and more custom icons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During beta testing, we included an option for folks to be able to use the service for free. This has been a huge help
for us to work out the kinks and get some great feedback.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next week, we&amp;#39;ll be removing the ability for new users to sign up for the free account. We&amp;#39;ll continue supporting the
free plans for everyone who signed up early as a thank you for helping us out early on. So THANK YOU!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;re looking for a great free option for using Font Awesome, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bootstrapcdn.com/#fontawesome_tab&quot;&gt;BootstrapCDN&lt;/a&gt;
is fantastic. As always, thanks to the venerable &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.maxcdn.com/&quot;&gt;MaxCDN&lt;/a&gt; for hosting!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Black Tie coming in February!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m putting the finishing touches on Black Tie, the multi-weight, commercial icon font I
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/232193852/font-awesome-black-tie&quot;&gt;Kickstarted&lt;/a&gt; last year. As soon as it&amp;#39;s ready,
we&amp;#39;ll be adding this icon set to the Freelancer, Studio, and Agency plans in February.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Changes Based on Feedback&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on great feedback from our early users, we&amp;#39;re working on making a few changes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No credit card required for free trial&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yearly billing options&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Options for kit download&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Commercial icon sets!&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;#39;re working on a few deals to bring some absolutely amazing icon sets into Fonticons. We&amp;#39;ll keep you posted with any news!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
      <link>http://blog.fonticons.com/2015/01/29/changes-and-updates/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.fonticons.com/2015/01/29/changes-and-updates/</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year, New Feature, and New Updates!</title>
      <description>&lt;h3&gt;Custom Icons!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Everything’s shiny, Cap’n.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What could possibly be better than adding a sweet icon to your kit from one of our family of icon fonts?
Why, a most excellent icon you designed yourself, of course!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dave and I are really pumped to announce the
availability of custom icons in Fonticons. Upload your SVG, then you can add your custom icon to any of your kits.
We&amp;#39;re already using this feature today on the blog!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to some great user feedback, our Free plan now has the ability to try out
custom icons as well! We really think you&amp;#39;re going to love adding your own custom icons.
And if you don&amp;#39;t yet have a Fonticons account, you can &lt;a href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/request/new&quot;&gt;request an invite&lt;/a&gt; today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Font Awesome Black Tie&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Black Tie is going through some finishing touches, and Dave says it should be ready soon. We are happy to announce that
Black Tie will be available for our Freelancer, Studio, and Agency plans!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Font Awesome 4.3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Font Awesome 4.3 should be coming soon, and we&amp;#39;ll have it added to Fonticons shortly thereafter. Make sure you get in your icon
requests added to &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/FortAwesome/Font-Awesome/issues&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Thank You!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you to all those that have signed up and tried out Fonticons. We are constantly striving to make
Fonticons the best platform for icons on the web. We appreciate all feedback and hope to make 2015 a banner
year.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <link>http://blog.fonticons.com/2015/01/02/new-year-new-feature-new-updates/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.fonticons.com/2015/01/02/new-year-new-feature-new-updates/</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invites and Custom Icons</title>
      <description>&lt;h3&gt;Invitations are going out!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Travis and I are crazy excited (yep, again), because we just sent out the first batch of Fonticons Beta invitations!
We&amp;#39;re rolling them out slowly to make sure everything goes smoothly. If you already
&lt;a href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/request/new&quot;&gt;requested for an invitation&lt;/a&gt;, you should be getting it in the next few days!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any issues or usability suggestions, please please talk to us! As we said in our last post, the easiest
way to get in touch with us is our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hipchat.com/g1K5ugavM&quot;&gt;public channel on HipChat&lt;/a&gt; (during US business
hours). Otherwise, hit us up on email at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:dave@fonticons.com&quot;&gt;dave@fonticons.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:travis@fonticons.com&quot;&gt;travis@fonticons.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Up Next: Custom Icons&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, we&amp;#39;re working on implementing custom icons for the beta. I&amp;#39;ve mapped out use cases, workflows, and the
HTML &amp;amp; CSS prototypes are ready to go. Today, Travis is starting implementation. We&amp;#39;re expecting to have those ready
sometime in the next month.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <link>http://blog.fonticons.com/2014/11/05/invites-and-custom-icons/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.fonticons.com/2014/11/05/invites-and-custom-icons/</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Fonticons</title>
      <description>&lt;p class=&quot;info initial-icon&quot;&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;icon icon-news&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
After several months of hard work, &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/supercodepoet&quot;&gt;Travis&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/davegandy&quot;&gt;I&lt;/a&gt; are crazy excited to announce a limited release of the Fonticons beta.
Interested? Head on over to &lt;a href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/request/new&quot;&gt;request an invitation&lt;/a&gt; and we&#39;ll get you one
as soon as we can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Fonticons makes web icons fast and easy.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;
With Fonticons, you&amp;#39;ll be able to choose just the right icon set to match the look and feel of your website and get
just the icons and CSS you need &amp;mdash; making your site load faster.
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Icon Fonts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think this is the beginning of a beautiful friendship.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Icon fonts are a great way to get scalable vector graphics on your website and have complete control over them with
CSS. That&amp;#39;s why I created &lt;a href=&quot;http://fontawesome.io&quot;&gt;Font Awesome&lt;/a&gt; a couple of years ago. Font Awesome gives you a
large set of scalable vector icons for just about anything your site needs. Font Awesome&amp;#39;s CSS features make it even
easier to use icons at larger sizes, as bullets, or even spin, stack, and rotate icons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://meanpath.com/f/HcZE2d&quot;&gt;According to meanpath&lt;/a&gt;, Font Awesome is now on almost 3 million websites. And we
continue to see more and more traffic every month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Why Fonticons?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I&amp;#39;m your huckleberry.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As simple and powerful as icon fonts are to use, they aren&amp;#39;t perfect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, people visiting your website have to download every single icon in the set. Our research shows that most websites
only use around 20 icons total. Font Awesome, for example, has almost 500 icons. That&amp;#39;s a lot of icons going across the
wire that your site isn&amp;#39;t using. And there&amp;#39;s likely a good bit of CSS you don&amp;#39;t need either. That slows your site down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, what if your icon set doesn&amp;#39;t have the exact icon you need? Or what if you want to serve up your company logo?
Creating your own icon font is no simple task. You&amp;#39;ll need to learn a typesetting tool, figure out how font metrics work,
make your icons pixel perfect, export to the right webfont formats, figure out the CSS to integrate everything, then get
your web server to serve up the custom font to every browser without cross-site failures. It&amp;#39;s a big bag of hurt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Web icons should easier. That&amp;#39;s why we made Fonticons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Speed up Your Website&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Faster! Faster! Faster would be better!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since Fonticons allows you to load just the icons and CSS your website uses, you&amp;#39;ll drastically speed up their load time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, if this blog were using stock Font Awesome 4.2.0, our icons and CSS would weigh in at 87.4kB.
Using Fonticons, this blog&amp;#39;s kit weighs in at 4.06kB. That&amp;#39;s a &lt;strong&gt;95% bandwidth savings&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Tons of Icon Sets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We need to talk about your flair.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like Helvetica isn&amp;#39;t the perfect typographic font for every website on earth, one single icon set isn&amp;#39;t
perfect for everyone either. The right set of icons reinforces the exact look and feel you need. We believe iconography
should have the same level of variety, beauty, and refinement seen in traditional typography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To give you the best icon sets to choose from, we&amp;#39;ve scoured the web and heavily curated just the right ones. We&amp;#39;ve made
sure each set has a large number of icons, so you&amp;#39;ll be more likely to find the perfect icon when you need it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Curious? &lt;a href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/fonts&quot;&gt;Check out our icon sets &amp;raquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We&amp;#39;re carefully adding new icon sets as we find just the right ones. Think we&amp;#39;re missing a set?
&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:dave@fonticons.com&quot;&gt;Let me know&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Powerful, Simple CSS Toolkit&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I&amp;#39;m giving her all she&amp;#39;s got, Captain!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;ve paired the best icon sets with Font Awesome&amp;#39;s powerful CSS toolkit. That makes it easier to control and style your
icons exactly the way you need. You can also pare down to just the CSS your site needs, making your kit load even faster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Served up from a CDN&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“She&amp;#39;ll make it point-five past lightspeed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;ve partnered up with &lt;a href=&quot;http://maxcdn.com&quot;&gt;MaxCDN&lt;/a&gt; to serve your icons wicked fast. Their global network means your kit
loads faster and more reliably anywhere in the world. Even our free accounts are served by MaxCDN!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;PS. We love you, MaxCDN. You&amp;#39;ve been hosting Font Awesome on BootstrapCDN since the early days. You&amp;#39;re awesome!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Custom Icons &amp;mdash; COMING SOON!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Good. Now I know what to get you for your birthday.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to add your company logo to your kit? Or anything else you can imagine? Fonticons makes it easy to upload and
manage your own custom vector icons. We&amp;#39;re adding this to Fonticons right now, so it should be ready soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Beta?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Boy, that escalated quickly&amp;hellip;”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now, Fonticons is a beta product. To us, that means you might occasionally run into an issue here or there. Let us
know ASAP, and we&amp;#39;ll get it fixed up quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Talk to Us&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Message for you, sir.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every day, we&amp;#39;re making Fonticons better. Improving reliability, adding features, simplifying the user experience. But
we can&amp;#39;t do that alone. We need your input and feedback to constantly make things better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;d love to hear from you. Our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hipchat.com/g1K5ugavM&quot;&gt;public channel on HipChat&lt;/a&gt; is the
best way to talk to us during normal US business hours. If we&amp;#39;re not around on HipChat, try emailing us at
&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:dave@fonticons.com&quot;&gt;dave@fonticons.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:travis@fonticons.com&quot;&gt;travis@fonticons.com&lt;/a&gt;. We&amp;#39;ll get back to you as soon as we can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Request an Invitation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Aaaaaas&amp;hellip; Yoooooou&amp;hellip; Wiiiiiish&amp;hellip;”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Want to try out Fonticons? Head on over to &lt;a href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/request/new&quot;&gt;request an invitation&lt;/a&gt; and we&amp;#39;ll get you
one soon. We&amp;#39;re adding new users just as fast as we can.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;sign-up&quot; href=&quot;https://fonticons.com/request/new&quot;&gt;Request an Invitation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <link>http://blog.fonticons.com/2014/10/23/introducing-fonticons/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://blog.fonticons.com/2014/10/23/introducing-fonticons/</guid>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
